Welcome to section four.
-: Bem vindo a seo quatro.
A lot of beginners struggle with what we're going to cover
Muitos iniciantes lutam com o que
in this section, which is object-oriented programming.
vamos cobrir nesta seo, que  programao orientada a objetos.
The way we've constructed this course,
Da maneira como construmos este
I'm sure you're not gonna have any difficulties whatsoever
curso, tenho certeza de que voc no ter qualquer
in understanding what object-oriented programming is about
dificuldade em entender o que  programao orientada a
and also how to use it in Python.
objetos e tambm como us-lo em Python.
Object-oriented programming is going to allow our programmes
A programao orientada a objetos permitir que nossos
to start talking about things that happen in the real world,
programas comecem a falar sobre coisas que acontecem no mundo
after all programming is a tool to convert data
real, afinal a programao  uma ferramenta para
from the real world into something we can use in programmes.
converter dados do mundo real em algo que podemos usar em programas.
Object-oriented programming is essential for us,
A programao orientada a objetos  essencial
the programmers, to understand more about how that happens.
para ns, os programadores, entendermos mais sobre como isso acontece.
I'll see you in the next video.
Eu vou te ver no prximo vdeo.